tazinga.com 2009-12-31

# Tazinga!

This PRIVACY POLICY (this "Policy") relates to the use of this website, TAZINGA™.COM, (the "Site") and is applicable to all information collected about you through the Site.

We ("we", "us" or "our") disclose the information collection and usage practices applicable to the Site in this Policy. This Policy describes the types of information that we collect from you on this Site and the other people who may also visit the Site (the "Users") and how we may use that information. By providing any information, you agree to our use of that information consistent with this Policy.

Please read this Policy carefully before providing us with any information. If you have questions about this Policy, e-mail us at [Contact Us](mailto:%69%6e%66%6f@%74%61%7a%69%6e%67%61.%63%6f%6d).

## How We Handle Information

We log your Internet Protocol ("IP") address in order to help us to diagnose problems with our server, administer the Site and track usage statistics. Your IP address may vary each time you visit, or it may be the same, depending on whether you access the Site through an always-on type of Internet connection (such as cable or DSL), or through a dial-up connection. Either way, it would be very difficult for us to personally identify you through your IP address. If you reached the Site by clicking on a link or ad from another website, then we may also log that information. This helps us to maximize our Internet exposure and to understand the interests of our Users. All of this information is collected and used only in aggregated form; that is, it is entered into our database, where we can use it to generate overall anonymous reports on our Users.

In addition, we will share your IP address, along with any search term used by you while conducting a query, with our advertising partners. This information will not be linked with any personal information.

## Cookies

We may place a small file known as a "cookie" on your computer's hard drive. A cookie may contain information that allows us to track your path through the Site and to determine whether you have visited us before. However, the cookies will not contain any information that would allow us to personally identify you. Our cookies cannot be used to read data from your hard drive and cannot retrieve information from any other cookies created by other websites. We use cookies in this manner to help us understand how Users use the Site, and to help us to improve the Site. You may refuse to accept a cookie from us by following the procedures for rejecting cookies specific to your web browser. Although you may do so, you may find that some aspects of the Site may not function properly without cookies. 

## Clear GIFs

We also employ a software technology called "clear gifs," which helps us better manage content on the Site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with unique identifiers, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on websites and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. 

If you visit this Site by "clicking through" from another website, and you have registered with that other website, then certain information about you that you provided to that other website, such as the terms you were searching on that led you to the Site, may be transmitted to us and we may use it. You should carefully review the privacy policy of any website from which you reached the Site in order to determine what information was collected by that website and for what purpose(s) you agreed that website could use that information. We may or may not retain that information; if we do, then we will only use it in accordance with this Policy.

## Policy Regarding Children Under the Age of 13

The Site is not intended for children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect or use any information from children under the age of 13.

## How We Use the Information We Collect

We may use the information that you provide to us to, among other things:

  * Make your next visit to the Site more personalized.
  * Compile anonymous statistical information and analysis.
  * Provide compiled anonymous information to third parties.
  * Provide, sell or rent your information to third parties for advertising purposes.

## Consent to the Use of Third Party Providers

Please understand that we may contract with other third parties to provide various services relating to the Site on an outsourced basis rather than performing the services ourselves. For example, we may contract with a website hosting provider to host the Site for us. By visiting the Site, all Users consent to us providing all information (whether or not personally identifiable) received or collected from those Users to such third party providers for the purpose of enabling the third party provider to provide these outsourced services to us. In addition, all Users consent to the collection, maintenance, and processing of their information (whether or not personally identifiable) by us and these third party providers.

We may also contract with other third party companies to collect data relating to our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertising 'click-throughs', and/or other activities on our website. Where permitted by us, such companies may also use cookies or other monitoring technologies to collect this data about our website visitors. All collected data is anonymous except where agreed to in advance by the individual website user. Data collected by such companies in accordance with this Policy may also be made available to the company's third party service providers. 

## Opting Out

This Policy describes our potential uses of your information. If you do not agree to our potential uses of your information as we have described for you in this Policy, you are not required to provide that information to us and you may opt out from any further access or use of the Site. 

## Other Websites and Links

Please be aware that our promotional partners, advertisers, sponsors, and other third-party websites accessible through the Site may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. We are not responsible or liable for any actions, content of websites or privacy policies of such third parties. You should review the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing any information (whether or not personally identifiable information) through linked websites.

## Disclosure of Your Information

As you might expect, we must cooperate with legal authorities, and may in some circumstances be required to disclose the information you provided (whether or not personally identifiable information) in response to requests from law enforcement authorities, or in response to a subpoena or other legal process. We don't expect this to happen, but if it does, we will provide only the information required. We can also turn over information about you if we believe we must in order to prevent a violation of the law, and by accepting this Policy, you consent to our right to do so, in our sole discretion. You also consent to our disclosing information about you in the course of legal proceedings if we believe we are legally required to do so, if we reasonably believe that doing so may mitigate our liability, or if doing so will assist us in enforcing our legal rights.

At some point we may establish subsidiaries, divisions, or other related companies. When that happens, then we may disclose your information to those related companies, in which case we will request those related companies to abide by this Policy or their own company policy, if appropriate and applicable. We may also disclose some information to a potential acquirer, although such disclosure would be subject to normal and customary confidentiality requirements.

## Notice

If we change this Policy, we will post the amended Policy on the Site so that you are aware of any changes or additions that have been made relating to what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, so please visit and review the Site frequently for any changes or modifications. Any such changes or amendments to this Policy will be effective when posted on the Site. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted, the revised Policy by your continued access and use of our services or the Site.

## Security

Of course, we will take reasonable measures to secure the information Users provide to us, using industry-standard methods. All information is protected by password and accessible only to authorized User personnel. However, there is a remote possibility that Internet transmissions containing a User's personally identifiable information, if provided, may be intercepted by others. There is no way for us to ensure the total and complete privacy of User information before it arrives at the Site or after it leaves the Site. Accordingly, we do not undertake any responsibility or liability for such events.

If you have questions specifically about this Policy, or to issues pertaining to the practices of the Site or your use of the Site, please contact us.

## Contact Information

E-mail: [Contact Us](mailto:%69%6e%66%6f@%74%61%7a%69%6e%67%61.%63%6f%6d)

Effective Date: 12/01/08

Copyright © 2008-2009 Tazinga. All rights reserved.
